rextester.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy policy, 2019

**Who we are**

Our website address is: https://rextester.com 

**What personal data we collect and why we collect it**

When you log in, we will set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

Internally we keep a login name and hashed version of your password if you use simple form to login or a hashed version of your email if you use Google login.

Display name that you choose while registering for the site is publicly visible.

**Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to track traffic, we don’t hold any data at our servers.

**Information collected**

Rextester does not collect personal information about you except for the information that you voluntarily provide.

We may collect usage information of our site to analyze interest in content and to provide advertisers information on an aggregate basis.

No personally identifiable information will be shared with third-party advertising companies.

Code snippets that have been saved without logging in first are publicly visible and are in a public domain.

Code snippets that have been saved by a logged in user without indicating that they are private are publicly visible and are in a public domain.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Rextester then you may contact me through the contact form on Feedback page.

Best Regards,  
The Rextester Team
